var geoQuestions = [
{
	"question": "Where is the great Barrier Reef?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["Africa", "N.America", "S.America", "Asia", "Australia"],
	"correctChoice": "Australia",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "Where is United States?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["Africa", "N.America", "S.America", "Asia", "Australia"],
	"correctChoice": "N.America",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "Where is Brazil?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["Africa", "N.America", "S.America", "Asia", "Australia"],
	"correctChoice": "S.America",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "Which country has the biggest land?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["Korea", "China", "United States", "Russia", "Australia"],
	"correctChoice": "Russia",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "Where is the Greatwall?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["Africa", "N.America", "S.America", "Asia", "Australia"],
	"correctChoice": "Asia",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "Where is the Mt. Fuji?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["Japan", "China", "United States", "Canada", "Australia"],
	"correctChoice": "Japan",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "Where is Tahoe Lake?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["Arizona", "Illinois", "Iowa", "Alaska", "California"],
	"correctChoice": "California",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "Where is the Japan?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["Africa", "N.America", "S.America", "Asia", "Australia"],
	"correctChoice": "Asia",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What planet is Curiosity Rover on now?",
	"questionType": 2,
	"correctAnswer": "Mars",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What is China bigger than Russia? Yes/No",
	"questionType": 2,
	"correctAnswer": "No",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What planet is Curiosity created?",
	"questionType": 2,
	"correctAnswer": "Earth",
	"score": 10
}];




var mathQuestions = [
{
	"question": "What is 1+1?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["2", "3", "0", "-1", "34"],
	"correctChoice": "2",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What is 23-10?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["12", "13", "20", "-31", "34"],
	"correctChoice": "13",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What is 45+30?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["75", "3", "0", "-1", "34"],
	"correctChoice": "75",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What is 4 x 4?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["12", "13", "10", "16", "34"],
	"correctChoice": "16",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What is 2 x 16?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["23", "32", "777", "-1", "34"],
	"correctChoice": "32",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What is 9 x 9?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["321", "231", "0", "81", "4"],
	"correctChoice": "81",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What is 8*8/8/8?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["24", "32", "23", "1", "75"],
	"correctChoice": "1",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What is 2^3?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["2", "8", "0", "72", "42"],
	"correctChoice": "8",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What is 67-4?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["63", "67", "21", "-1", "34"],
	"correctChoice": "63",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "what is 12 x 12?",
	"questionType": 2,
	"correctAnswer": "144",
	"score": 10
},

{
	"question": "what is 15 x 15?",
	"questionType": 2,
	"correctAnswer": "225",
	"score": 10
}];




var wotQuestions = [
{
	"question": "What tier is American T29 Tank?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10"],
	"correctChoice": "7",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What type of tank is American T29 tank",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["SPG", "Heavy Tank", "Tank Destroyer", "Medium Tank", "Light Tank"],
	"correctChoice": "Heavy Tank",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What is the best gun can be mounted on the IS-3?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["BL-9", "BL-10", "BL-7", "LB-1", "D-54"],
	"correctChoice": "BL-9",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "Where is thickness of front turret armor of T-54?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["190mm", "50mm", "200mm", "240mm", "170mm"],
	"correctChoice": "200mm",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "Where is the alpha damage of the AT gun T7 mounted on T30?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["256", "276", "311", "750", "560"],
	"correctChoice": "750",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What tier is American Tank Destryer T30?",
	"questionType": 2,
	"correctAnswer": "9",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What tier is American T20 Tank?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10"],
	"correctChoice": "7",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What tier is American T29 Tank?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10"],
	"correctChoice": "7",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What tier is American T110E5 Tank?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10"],
	"correctChoice": "10",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "What tier is Russian T54 Tank?",
	"questionType": 1,
	"choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10"],
	"correctChoice": "9",
	"score": 10
},
{
	"question": "Does Chinese tech tree in World of tanks has a SPG line?",
	"questionType": 2,
	"correctAnswer": "No",
	"score": 10
}];
